(Sheldon:)I don't want
to play anymore.
(Leonard:)We haven't been on a road trip
in a while.
(Leonard:)This is fun.
(Sheldon:)We get it-- you won the game.
(Sheldon:)Stop bragging.
(Leonard:)No, listen, we wrote
a paper together.
(Leonard:)Now we get to go to a university
and talk about it?
(Leonard:)That's pretty cool.
(Sheldon:)I suppose it is.
(Sheldon:)In fact, if you'd like to
celebrate with a little music,
(Sheldon:)I'd be okay with that.
(Leonard:)What...?
(Leonard:)This road trip just got crazy.
(Sheldon:)Play that funky music,
white boy.
(Leonard:)I'm surprised you know
that reference.
(Sheldon:)What reference?
(Bernadette:)So, I put stickers
on everything we're gonna sell.
(Bernadette:)We just need help taking it
all out to the driveway.
(Amy:)Can I be in charge
of pricing?
(Amy:)I've been going to garage
sales my whole life.
(Amy:)Can you believe I got these
pantyhose for a nickel?
(Howard:)All right, Amy's in charge
of pricing and being 75.